

Iryna Buina

+48 733 286 194

Krakow, Poland (considering relocation)

PROFILE

Responsible, outgoing selfstarter with a passion for customer service and safety and more than three years of experience in customer service and team management fields. looking to fill the position for a flight attendant with Emirates, where my hospitality and customer service skills will best serve customers.

SKILLS

- Amiability and excellent communication skills.
- Adaptability.
- Successful at working in culturally diverse team.
- Stress resilience.
- Problem-solving and negotiation skills.
- Persuasion.
- 162cm tall, reaching 220cm on tippy toes.
- Vision: -2 (same since 2017).
- 23 years old.

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian

Russian

English

German

Polish

WORK EXPERIENCE

Workflow Leader (promoted)(ENG) Majorel, Krakow Apr 2023 - Sep 2023

- Provided clear communication between different teams in the multicultural environment.
- Made sure, that all the safety and privacy policies were complied with and in case of emergency was responsible for the evacuation of our floor.
- Coloborated with team of trainrers in approaching and training new hires. Provided newbies with any sort of clarification and helped them to adapt better.
- Created a schedule for the team, tracked daily attendance, and ensured compliance with tasks by the entire team.
- Prepared and presented Weekly Business Review.

Content reviwer(ENG) Majorel, Krakow Mar 2022 - Apr 2023

Account manager (ENG) Atlasiko inc., Vinnytsia Nov 2020 - Mar 2022

Customer service specialist (ENG)
Omio(German travel comparison and booking website), Vinnytsia
Jul 2019 - Oct 2020

- Delievered high-level customer support by inline call and email servises with average index of 98.2% customer satisfaction.
- Kept connection between customer and travel companies.
- Attentivelly ammended and cancelled clients' booking when needed.
- Provided customers with alternative ways for them to handle the request when the company authority was not enough.

Hostess(promoted) McDonald's, Vinnytsia Dec 2018 - July 2019

- Greeted the customers and helped them with any inqueries that may happen during their stay.
- Approached guests and comunicated with other teams to provide safe and friendly atmosphere in the restaurand.
- Hosted children Birthday parties.
- Led the team of 5-10 people in order to keep the restaurant clean and safe.

Service crew member McDonald's, Vinnytsia Feb 2018 - Dec 2018

• Helped customers to chose and order food of their likings.

EDUCATION

 VSPU named after M. Kotsyubynsky, Faculty of Foreign Languages 2017 - 2021

 Vinnytsia Gymnasium school 30, with a focus on foreign languages.

2007 - 2017